Ooh- hooh-
La la la la~
You still see my shadow in your room.
Can't run back and leave us behind you.
It's to the point where I'm going to kill you-
-and I'm gonna eat you so I must remove your bones.
Easier said than done,
I thought you were the one,
Draining all of your heart-
-dissecting your head.
I found another one-
-but you are the better one-
-I won't let you escape me.
I'll make sure that you will-
-end up inside your grave.
You know that I want your head.
You fear these lucid dreams,
Where you can't move a thing.
Blood dripping off of your bed.
I'll do it over again
I just want you to end
Watch ashes blow in the wind,
You should've listened to your friends
Did this shit in the past,
Do not want you to last,
You were made out of fleshy steak.
You were tangled up in your bed for days.
Who knew demon girls had the tastiest fate.
Took away your heart now your life is at stake.
Now I ate your heart and made you
Now I ate your heart and made you break.
I'll make your heart break.
I'll make your heart ache.
I'll make your heart break again.
You still see my shadow in your room.
Can't run back and leave us behind you.
It's to the point where I'm going to kill you-
-and I'm gonna eat you so I must remove your bones.
Easier said than done,
I thought you were the one,
Draining all of your heart-
-dissecting your head.
I found another one-
-but you are the better one-
-I won't let you escape me.
Did this shit in the past,
Do not want you to last,
You were made out of fleshy steak.
You were tangled up in your bed for days.
Who knew demon girls had the tastiest fate.