I was tryin' to find a way to kill time
I didn't even get to tell you goodbye
Now you're gone and I can't ever say goodbye
This feeling's goin' to my head,
I'm thinkin' things I shouldn't say
You circled me inside my room,
I couldn't
I couldn't go
I couldn't go, go
I couldn't go, go, go
I couldn't go, go, go, go
Oh my god, what the fuck?
Take my hand, crush it up
Spill the blood on the floor,
I ain't scared, think there's more
What the fuck? Make it stop,
Took too long, here right now
On the floor, in the car,
Smokin' cigs in the bar
I don't want you to think
I got bad intentions
Never wanted you inside
You made it your mission, yeah (Yeah)
Didn't wanna hurt no one
But you just went and made it fun, fun, fun, fun
Hear you're lookin' for a
Way to fight the Corpus bride
She's workin' in my mind
And you're lookin' for a
Way to crush, it's not enough
You fucked up your last try, you cannot try (Last try)
We were in the studio, I was just playin'
You were all work and I was all play and
You were talkin' business, aimin' with your weapon
I was on your hit list, I felt the compression