Think of these thoughts as limitless light
Exposing, closing
Circuitry of fright
Think of each moment
Holding this breath
As death minute in decimal
Resident Boyfriend, how do you plead
We'll need your testimony on the stand
Solemnly swear to tell the whole truth
So help you, son, now raise your right hand
Condemn him to the infirmary
All mine towers crumble down
The flowers gasping under rubble
Shrieking in the hall of lull
Thy genius sates a thirst for trouble
Here in my kingdom, I am your lord
I order you to cower and pray
Nuns commence incanting as the
Lightning strikes mine temples thus
Electrifying mine chambers wholly
Scorching out thine sovereignty
See how the serfs work the ground
(See how they fall)
And they give it all they've got
(Fall)
And you give it all you've got till you're down
Ha
Ha ha
Ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha
See how the brain plays around
And you fall inside a hole you couldn't see
And you fall inside a hole inside a
Understand what's going on inside my mind
Never they ponder whether electric
Calming if you look at it right