Your
Your boy
Your boy boy
Your boy boy boy
Your boy boy boy boy
Your boy boy boy boy boyfriend
Have you ever had the feeling you're drawn to someone?
Yeah
And it isn't anything they could've said or done
And everyday I see you on your own.
And I can't believe that you're all alone.
But I overheard your girls and this what they said
Looking for a
Looking for a, looking for a
Can't you see? All I really wanna be.
Is your Boyfriend™. Can't fight that
Knock me down, you know, I'm coming right back
I don't care at all what you done before
All I really want is to be your.
Let me take a little moment to find the right words
To find the right
So when I kick it to you it ain't something that you've heard
Something that you've
I don't know what kind of guy that you prefer
But I know I gotta put myself for worse
See I think I got the kind of love that you deserve and I heard that
Can't you see? All I really wanna be.
Is your Boyfriend™. Can't fight that
Knock me down, you know, I'm coming right back
I don't care at all what you done before
All I really want is to be your.